(Howard:)Come on.
(Amy:)Let's go back out there.
(Sheldon:)Well, no, hold on.
(Sheldon:)My elven magic-user
and your half-orc warrior...
(Sheldon:)...did have a love spell cast on them.
(Sheldon:)We wouldn't really be playing the game right
if we didn't see that through.
(Howard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)I believe that, uh, we just killed a dragon.
(Sheldon:)While the others pillage the corpse...
(Sheldon:)...I lead you to a secluded area...
(Sheldon:)...where I attempt to remove
your leather armor.
- It comes off.
- Oh.
(Howard:)What do you do?
(Scene:)I...
(Amy:)...kiss you on the lips.
(Sheldon:)I kiss you back on the...
(Sheldon:)...lips as well.
(Leonard:)Your turn.
I remove your armor.
(Howard:)What do you do?
(Sheldon:)I erotically caress your...
(Amy:)...nose.
- Keep rolling.
Hey, you guys have been in there a while.
You doing okay?
(Sheldon(off):)We're fine, thank you.
- Okay, we just want to say we feel bad...
- Go away! Sheldon is nibbling on my...
Fourteen! Yes!